[Verse 1]
Another head hangs lowly
Child is slowly taken
And the violence caused such silence
Who are we, mistaken?

[Pre-Chorus]
But you see, it's not me, it's not my family
In your head, in your head, they are fightin'
With their tanks and their bombs and their bombs and their guns
In your head, in your head, they are cryin'

[Chorus]
In your head, in your head
Zombie, zombie, zombie-ie-ie
What's in your head, in your head?
Zombie, zombie, zombie-ie-ie-ie, oh

[Post-Chorus]
Doo, doo, doo, doo
Doo, doo, doo, doo
Doo, doo, doo, doo
Doo, doo, doo, doo

[Verse 2]
Another mother's breakin'
Heart is takin' over
When the violence causes silence
We must be mistaken
